Hello everyone, we are not by call me, and this is Natsumi & Shiori's Welcome Back Party!
Welcome back!
I can hear everyone's voice, can't you?
We're so happy to have you two back, and we'd like to welcome you back to the Joy Channel for the first time since you came back to the show.
This is the first time for them to appear on the Joy Channel since they came back to the show.
So this time, we're going to have a relaxed home party.
I'm so happy!
During the break, we've been able to see each other individually, but I'd like to hear what you two have to say.
I've been listening to Ivy's music a lot.
Oh, that's right.
We too.
I've been listening to it a lot.
What have you been listening to?
I'm listening to Holoburst Risk and The Secret Stone.
Oh, great.
I'm Miracle.
But they're both so refreshing.
I've been watching the music videos and rehearsal videos too.
Oh, really?
I've been wanting to watch them more than ever.
I see.
I discovered something new.
We were also asked to sing by proxy... and we were asked to sing parts of their songs.
So, before the show, during rehearsals, I'd hear myself singing their parts over and over again, and I'd think, "They're lucky to have me.
I'm happy.
The waves are growing, too.
Yeah, it's getting brighter.
You know...
You know, when I first met you... you scared the shit out of me.
I couldn't stop looking twice.
I think it was a recording.
You didn't say anything, you just said, "Hi," and "good morning.
What? Like, "Good morning.
Surprise.
I gave him a surprise.
I've always wanted to do that.
I see.
High school students come to Moomi in the summer.
That's right.
You graduated, right?
Natsumi.
What are you going to do?
I'm asking you for your JK spirit.
OK.
For 11 students.
You'll be carrying 11 JKs on your back.
That's for sure.
Thank you for your hard work on this one.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
It's like living a life of immortality... usually.
Natsumi was probably recuperating from her back injury.
Do you have any hobbies that you enjoyed?
Sure.
I enjoy anime and manga.
I enjoyed those hobbies.
I did enjoy them a little.
I see.
My favorite...
What was it? On Sundays?
Oh, um...
Sentai?
Sentai.
I watched it.
I was watching it.
It's cool.
It's so cool.
I've been on vacation.
I've been feeling the members every day.
Oh, wow.
That Moe...
Before my vacation...
I mean...
She signed the photo card
She signed it and wrote "Good luck!" on it.
A good-luck charm.
He wrote "good luck charm" on it.
I carry it with me every day during the winter.I carry it around with me every day, like in the winter time.
Look at that.
Moe
I'm so happy.
That's nice.
You put it up.
I used to put it on my wall every day.
He started carrying it around with him in the winter.
That's great.
That's reassuring.
I'm going on my first pilgrimage.
It's like...
The shrine Chiichan and I went to two years ago.
And with Natsumi...
Natsumi and I went to Hanazono Shrine.
The two of us.
Natsumi's back is better.
I wish you good luck, Chii-chan.
I bought a good-luck charm.
But did I give it to her?
I did.
It's called "The Thunderbolt".
Yes, it is.
The color is like mint cream.
I still gave it to Chii-chan.
If I don't lose...
I'll give it to you next time.
Thank you.
And stationery, too.
I bought her a stationery set, too, to wish her good luck.
But I haven't given it to you yet.
You haven't?
Let's go together.
I'm sure Mirei will give you a pen pouch before bedtime.
That's right.
I just wanted to wish you good luck.
Thank you.
I really love you guys.
I really do.
I really love this time at Ini.
I thought again how wonderful you all are.
I really like you as a member
I was able to see Noini from an objective point of view
I respect them as an idol.
What?
What, what, what?
Very much.
They're a wonderful group.
I personally came back as Natsumi.
Natsumi's love for Mirei...
Natsumi's love for even Mirei was as explosive as ever.
It's hard.
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting.
I'm waiting.
It's open.
That's great.
Maybe we're making some progress.
There might be a breakthrough.
I got a little carried away.
I've got a lot of candy in front of me.
And today...
They've prepared a game for us.
Yay!
This is a switch, right?
That's right!
Switch.
That's great.
Can you make it today?
We're having a media party.
Oh, yeah!
He wants to have fun.
Yeah!
Media party.
I'm looking forward to it.
At this rate, we'll be talking for the rest of our lives.
I'm gonna be talking for the rest of my life.
We'll have some snacks and snacks.
I'd like to play games with everyone.
That's all I have to say.That's what I'm talking about.
We're all ready to go, but...
First of all, Miru-san...
Yes, I...
I chose "Yoshi".
Yoshi, Yoshi.
And Shiori...
I chose Lazy
I chose Casserly
I chose Mario.
Nice and colorful!
I'm going to play free-play from now on.
I'm going to play for free from now on.
Good night!
Carl, Egg Rare, something like that.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll leave it to you, Yaylander!
What's with the sleepy burn?
I have to put it in the chi-button.
Okay, I win.
Oh, okay, I'll win.
I'm gonna...
I'm up.
Don't get up.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay!
You're early, Daisy.
All right.
I knew it. Mario.
Mario?
Wow.
Uh, uh, no.
What, seriously?
What?
What do you mean?
Are we going back?
Oh, we have to go back.
I pushed it. I have to go back to the exit.
Let's do it again.
What? Are you sure? Let's do it again.
If you push it, it's over.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's good.
That's funny.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
owych.
Let's be bullish
Sarumasando
Oh!
Oh, really?
Oh, I'm sure you can do it. This time.
Oh!
It's growing.
Oh, yeah.
Yay!
Wait, that's a cute tree back there.
Cute.
Wow!
Wow, you're amazing!
Congratulations!
But only Natsumi didn't get to open it.
Ha-ha-ha!
What?
What other games do you have?
Hmm...
Maybe Horror Mansion.
Horror Mansion?
Mmm-hmm.
Let's go to the Mansion of Horrors, then.
Oh.
I think I can win this.
Let's go for it!
Oh!
Ooh.
Ooh.Ooh.
Go.
Where did you come from?
Oh, same floor.
Where did you go?
Oh, here we go.
I've been upstairs my whole life.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Staff downstairs.
The enemy is coming.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I may have found a trick.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Number one.
Oh, I'm down! I'm down!
Moe, you're fast!
It's gone up!
He got down!
Ah!
Hey.
I'm with you.
Hold on.
He's getting off.
He's getting out. - He's getting out.
Help me!
Scratch! Scratch! Scratch!
Agee, come down.
Scratch.
It's Moe.
Bye bye bye bye
Good morning.
- Daisy? Oh, no, it's too funny.
Well, that was fun.
Let's see...
- Penguins?
Um, ah...
Penguin March Street.
- Oh, so cute
- Otter Metsch's Otter Metsch
Yeah, dodging penguins
- I want to dodge the penguins.
So cute!
pea-oped
🐬
🐬 🐬
🐬 🐬 🐬
What do you think?
What do you want?
There it is! Down there on the left.
The bingo place?
Yeah!
There it is!
I thought it was there.
It's okay.
Oh, no, you mean that? That's what you mean?
Where am I supposed to be? Oh, this...
That hurts.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What was that?
And there's no one here.
Oh, there's two left.
Okay, Reijin, you got it.
Yay!
What the hell?
Let's all do it together!
Let's do it together.
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Normal mode
Endless ModeEndless Mode
What the hell is this?
Normal.
Okay, then Nakazawa will go.
Seino
One.
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wait, four times.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
Is that me?
Uh-huh.
Is it me?
That was fun.
Let's do it again.
Last one.
Seven.
I'll do my best.
Ennales.
Ennales?
What's the difference?
Hey.
Okay, everyone.
Let's do this. Let's do the target ten times.
That's right.
All of us.
Let's go for it.
The objective is changing.
Hey.
Let's do it.
One.
Two.
Three.
I'll do my best.
You got it.
I can do it.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
That was a little fast.
I stopped 10 times.
Mario again.
Mario.
Did I make it 10 times?
I did it!
You did it!
That was close!
We all made it 10 times!
I could do it!
It was fun!
But it was so cold!
It was cold!
That's what I'm saying.
We had some snacks and played some games.
How did you two do?
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! It's the best time to hang out with people like this.
I love it when we get to hang out with everyone like this!
Me too!
The best!
I'm so glad you made it!
Thank you very much.
How was it? It was a lot of fun, but next time we have another opportunity like this I will win.
I will do my best. I want to do it with 12 people together. I want to do it. I think we can do this.
If we play a tournament or something. After that, I'm sure you two will be appearing more and more on the Ika no Jou channel.
I'm sure you will be appearing more and more on the Ika-no-jou channel.
So, bye-bye!